{"data":[{"question":"All pilots are responsible for their passengers' safe.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wear","b":"when","c":"to walk","d":"at","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To walk->walking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The country air are fresh, moreover, it is not polluted.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"made","b":"conventional","c":"remark","d":"the","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Remark-> remarks","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"I always make a point of checking that all the windows are shut after I go out.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"look","b":"on","c":"with","d":"greatly","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Greatly-> great","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"We are having a little get-together to celebrate David promotion.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"feel","b":"certain","c":"with","d":"tomorrow","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- With-> of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"She is enough old to be independent of her parents.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"said","c":"me","d":"mistaken","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Was-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"You need attach a label to each piece with luggage.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"well","b":"handy","c":"to","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Well-> good","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"You should wear conspicuous clothes when to walk at night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of","b":"less","c":"trait","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Trait-> traits","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"She made a few conventional remark about the weather.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"was tooting","c":"as","d":"reached","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Toot-> tooted","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"She can look back on her career with greatly satisfaction.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Try","b":"to","c":"in","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"I feel a certain apprehension with my interview tomorrow.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"real","c":"herself","d":"for","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Real-> really","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"}]}